guidespot.com 2010-01-05

# Guidespot: Privacy Policy

  1.   2. We, Local Matters, Inc., respect the privacy of our visitors to our website, the home page of which is located at www.Guidespot.com (the "Website"). This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any personal information you submit to us through our website. "Personal Information" is information about you that is personally identifiable to you like your name, address, email address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. Please note that capitalized terms not defined herein have the meaning used in the Terms of Service. 

## Your Consent

By using our Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. You should visit this page periodically to review any changes to this Privacy Policy. 

## Information We Collect

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Website. If you create an account in order to access certain features and services, we may collect certain Personal Information such as your email address, a user name and password. If you email us directly via an e-mail hyperlink to provide us feedback or to ask us a question regarding our site or our business, we will collect any information contained in such email, and we will treat any such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide any such feedback to us, we may use such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. 

We will collect all information you submit via the Website, including any Personal Information. Please note that you are not obligated to provide any Personal Information to use the Guidespot.com Services other than any Personal Information required to register to become a Member 

If you decide to email search results, reviews, or other content to another individual through the Website, we will collect this individual's email address in order to send this email. We will also collect your name, email address, and any personal message you decide to include in the email. We will not send additional emails to this individual, unless you specifically request us to do so. 

As you navigate our Website, certain passive information will also be collected, including Internet Protocol addresses, cookies and navigational data. This type of information will be used in the aggregate for the purposes of gathering data to improve our Website, and to improve the quality of your experience when interacting with our Website. This information will not be linked with any Personal Information. 

## How We Use Your Information

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used to respond to requests that you make or to provide or improve our services. We will also use your Personal Information as directed by you. 

Any personally identifiable information you have included in your reviews may be shown to on the Website in conjunction with reviews you have contributed. 

Your Personal Information (e.g., name and e-mail address) may also be used when you send an email notification to a another user (such as in an invitation, or when sharing a review). We may also use your email address to send you updates or news regarding our site, but you may choose not to receive email of this type upon sign-up. Despite your indicated email preferences, we may have to send you notices of any updates to our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, or your account. 

Browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp data help us diagnose problems with our server, administer, and otherwise provide the highest possible level of service to you. In addition, we use this information to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, their advertising banners. 

## Disclosure of Personal Information

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information to third parties. We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on Guidespot.com; or (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Guidespot.com or any third party. 

Although we currently do not have a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, "affiliates"), we may in the future. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with these affiliates, in which case we will require our affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We will notify you when information about you may be provided to third parties in ways other than explained above, and you will have the option to prevent such information sharing. 

## Links

Our Website may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Guidespot.com does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy polices on these third party websites. 

## Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., username, e-mail address) via reviews, messages, forums, postings, or in other areas of the Website, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Guidespot.com. Please do not post any personal information on the Website or in other areas that you expect to keep private. As a registered Guidespot.com Member, you can modify your personal information at any time by updating your account 

## Regarding Children

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13. 

## Security

We use industry standard measures to maintain the security of your Personal Information. These measures include, but are not limited to, the use of a corporate firewall; storage of our software and servers in a secure co-location facility; the requirement of password-protection on Personal Information; Although we take industry standard measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information 

You hereby acknowledge that Guidespot.com is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner. 

## Privacy Policy Updates

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any substantial changes in the way we collect, use, or disclose your Personal Information, we will post a notice on this page. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Website. Continued use of our Website following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. 

## Contact Us

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 
    
        	Local Matters, Inc.
    	1221 Auraria Parkway
    	Denver, CO 80204
